

A highly motivated self-taught front-end developer with excellent problem solving skills specialising in JS, CSS and React. Passionate about building beautiful Front-end and CSS. I have keen interest in Bitcoin and deep into crypto stuff.

#### CONTACT

+62 813-3795-8068

☑ iamlexieonearth@gmail.com

in LinkedIn.com/in/alexandria-roberts-001/

Casa Amata, Bali, Indonesia

#### EDUCATION

#### Master's Degree,

MSc International Management
University of Sussex
2010 – 2011

## Bachelor's Degree,

BE Computer Sci. & Engineering Sant Gadge Baba University, Amaravati 1997 – 2001

#### SKILLS

Core Competencies Web Development, Web Accessibility, Mentorship

Programming Languages
HTML, CSS, SASS, JavaScript, TypeScript

Libraries/Frameworks React]S, Redux, Next]S, ThemeUI, Storybook, TailWind, Vue]S, BootStrap

Git, Github, VSCode

## EXTRA

#### Achievements

I was awarded a full scholarship to study at University Of Sussex and was chosen to be 1 in 25 students from nearly 10,000 applicants.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **UI Engineer**

EDGE & NODE | 02/2022 - 11/2022

- Developed UIs and features in Next]s, React, ThemeUI and marketing pages in tight deadlines..
- Created a design system and developed components using storybook in Next]S.
- Collaborated with colleagues on a complex project to organize resources and enabled the delivery of a project on time.
- Refactored and optimized existing code.
- Improved performance for website by reducing load time by 62%.

# Front-End Developer Intern

APY VISION | 04/2021 - 12/2021

- Created UI's and features with SASS, Redux and React.
- Delivered marketing website using React framework
- Tested sites and applications in different browsers and environments before implementation to ensure deliverable.
- Problem solving and bug fixes in existing projects.
- Built features using different protocols, and chains using API's.

#### Founder, Full-Stack Developer

ROOOTS, Moziilla Builders Spring Open Lab | 04/2020 - 01/2021

Founded women mentorship platform, lead the team to organize the project.

- Developed the marketing site using VueJS & SASS
- Learned Node]S to integrate it into the platform.
- Hired volunteers in software development to marketing to help build it.

# Front-End Developer

JOYJET DIGITAL SPACE AGENCY | 09/2019 - 03/2020

- Developed new user-facing features in languages such as HTML5, CSS and JavaScript.
- Created sites using Divi in Wordpress.
- Created email design/UIs using Foundation Zurb for clients.
- Optimized applications for speed, scalability using Google Developer Tools and Lighthouse.

#### PERSONAL PROJECTS

# Display NFT's from Web3 Ethereal Wallet Address

Project which consists of Next)s, and using Alchemy's API to integrate with wallet, after entering the address shows the NFT's from that wallet.

## Flower Game

This project is built in Vue]S. This is the game in Vue]S where I fundamentally had to learn Vue]S from scratch as this was the first major app I worked on.